fxtechstrategy.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy - Read how your data is protected on our website

**Privacy Statement**

FXTechstrategy.com is committed to protecting the personal information that you submit to us. As a consequence, we guarantee never to deliberately disclose individually identifiable information about you to anybody.

**Personal Information**

When registering for our subscription services or newsletters and filling out our contact us form, we collect your email address, first and last names.

The information will be used to deliver either our subscriptions or newsletters to you and may also be used to inform you about the latest developments on the site and offers for other products and services from FXTechstrategy.

We do not share any personal information collected on this site with any third parties. None of the information that you give us is transferred, sold or rented to third parties.

**Use of Third Party Cookies**

Cookies may also allow FXTechstrategy to utilize third party marketing tools including, but not limited to, those offered by Google Adwords, Bing Ads etc. These tools may allow us track clicks, conversions and identify potential customers and visitors based on internet usage patterns and visited sites.

**Opting out of Future Communications and Deleting Personal Information.**

With newsletter, you will only add yourself to our newsletter list if you want to. In addition, all of FXTechstrategy’s email services are accompanied with a simple-to-use facility for unsubscribing. You may click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any or every email. This will remove you permanently from any or all subscribed lists.

## **Get the award-winning, easy-to-use daily forex analysis and trade ideas**

#### Join the 3,497+ traders using FXTechstrategy to improve their trading results
